[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "Who has the thickest skin, you or the rhino?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "Well, I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "How long is that going to last, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "INGRICH: I don't know, but I thought it was a very good sign.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ron Wyden"]}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", ":", "RB", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "-- it is a -- it is a radical -- but it is a radical form of social engineering, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "But -- well, but the current Ryan plan, which he developed with Senator Ron Wyden, a Democrat, the only bipartisan plan to save Medicare.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul Ryan"], "LOCATION": ["Georgetown"]}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "As a Catholic, what is your reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "Well, first of all, I would encourage everybody who's concerned about Catholic social doctrine to read Paul Ryan's remarkable speech at Georgetown in which he outlines his commitment to precisely the concerns of the church and helping the poor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "How would you describe that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "Wait -- wait a second, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ronald Reagan", "Jimmy Carter", "Ronald Reagan"]}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "No?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "Ronald Reagan had a deeper recession under Jimmy Carter and Ronald Reagan recovered in three years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "And I guess more importantly, what do you think about the guy who did get the gig?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "AWLENTY: I think it's a terrific pick.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Governor Romney"]}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "When you are being vetted, I mean -- how many years back do you have to go in the vetting process?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "Well, Governor Romney has committed to release two years of tax returns.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "I mean unless you've got something to hide, why wouldn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "I think his position's very reasonable, Piers, for this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Romney"]}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBD", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "If you were a guessing man, what percentage of the Ryan budget plan could you envisage a Romney presidency actually adopting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "Well, Governor Romney has said he's going to have his own plan and does have his own plan.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "Secretary of state maybe?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "You just don't quit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "But what is the Democrat view of the hyperbole that's now surrounding this guy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "Well, clearly, Piers, he's energizing the Republican Tea Party base.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "There's now a clear ideological difference for American people to vote on come November, isn't there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "Well, there is.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "How does the American voter cut through all this and actually come to a clear verdict on this plan, giving that he's now going to be the VP running mate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "DT", "CC", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "Well, Piers, I think they should first go and look at the plan and they should also look at the Democratic budget committee analysis of the plan.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "It's just how we get there, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "Well, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "Was I reading the ruins correctly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "Well, I think there's some of that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "How you doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "Welcome, sir.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "You finally got me, huh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "It's taken me nearly two years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CD", "NN", "RB", ",", "CD", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "-- than it has been, 20 years ago, in your experience, since you began making movies?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "I think that it's that whole thing, one step forward, one step back.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "What did you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "I said people thought he was Jesus.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "Where do you think if he gets re-elected he should push harder?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "The bottom line is economics.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "Did you like the Olympics?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "Say it again.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "Did you like the Olympics?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "Oh, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "You don't see I'm wearing my jacket?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "Wasn't bad, was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "You guys did great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "But has it made America more or less racist?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "RBR", "CC", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "I like to say, first of all, African-Americans alone did not elect President Obama.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Texas"]}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "Where?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "It was down in Texas I think.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "How many people die of gunshots in England every year?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "This is the point I make.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "The guy from Aurora, how can you buy that much ammunition on the Internet and that's not a red flag?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "There were never red flags.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Aurora"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Vulcan"]}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", ":", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "Well what do you do about NRA, which holds this incredible power?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "They got the -- the Vulcan death grip.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "Should -- should Barack Obama, rather than just talk in this kind of slightly rhetoric way, as he does about guns, should he now push?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", ":", "MD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "I think they both should.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 651, "question": "And then gone, how do you feel about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 652, "answer": "I'm over it now, but I -- it came out of nowhere.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 661, "question": "How are you going to feel when he comes to the Garden in a Houston shirt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 662, "answer": "Well, he's got to have to come down the lane.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Houston"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mike Tyson Show"], "LOCATION": ["Vegas"]}, "docId": "120813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 664, "question": "Hey, I'm not -- no blood, no foul, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 665, "answer": "You just finished doing the Mike Tyson Show, which I saw a fledgling version of it in Vegas.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]